A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Old Book Program - Authors Files, 5
  - Adams, Margaret - "Social and Ethical Issues in Medical Practice", May 13, 1974-February 26, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 322)
  - Adams, Paul L., October 7-16, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - Altenstetter, Christa - "Health Policy in the U.S. and West Germany", November 7, 1972-January 11, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 324)
  - American Medical Women's Association (Symposium), September 28, 1978-July 5, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 325)
  - Armstrong, Donald, May 2, 1977-March 1, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 326)
  - Association for the Study of Medical Education (Reports), September 14, 1965-April 2, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 327)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - "Longitudinal Study of Medical School Graduates of 1960", September 13, 1985-June 26, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 328)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges - "Longitudinal Study of Medical School Graduates of 1960", September 13, 1985-June 26, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 329)
  - Austin, Martha A. and Oswald Werner - "Navajo Ethno-medical Encyclopedia", November 3, 1978-April 30, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 330)
  - Beiser, Morton - "Navajo Singer", September 11, 1975-March 31, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 331)
  - Bernstein, I. A. - "Molecular Mechanisms of Biological Accomodation to Environmental Stressors", February 1, 1977-July 5, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 332)
  - Bice, Tom - "Health Care: An International Study", January 20, 1976-February 4, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 333)
  - Bing, Richard J. - "Scientific Background of Cardiology: It's History and Development", January 24, 1979-August 27, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 334)
  - Bloom, Samuel W. - "Contributions of Sociology to Medical Education", November 30, 1976-June 17, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 335)
  - Blumberg, Mark S. - "Health Manpower in the U.S. in the Seventies", May 15, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 336)
  - Blumberg, Mark S. - "Health Manpower in the U.S. in the Seventies", May 15-28, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 337)
  - Bonner, J. T., January 7, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 338)
  - Bordley, James - "Follow-up Study of Former Patients at Johns Hopkins", July 1, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 339)
  - Brenner, M. Harvey - "Economy and Mental Health", August 18, 1969-May 21, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 340)
  - Bunuel, Leonardo Garcia and Luis Guedes-Arroyo, August 18, 1969-May 21, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 341)
  - Burian, Herman M. [Grant-in-Aid], August 2, 1967-April 24, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 342)
  - Caplan, Gerald, July 24, 1970-September 29, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 343)
  - Capron, Alexander M. and Jay Katz - "Disclosure and Consent: Decision Making in Physician-Patient and Lawyer-Client Interactions", January 15, 1979-November 13, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 344)
  - Chase, Robert A. - "Bone Tumer Pathology", December 16, 1979-September 9, 1970~ (Box 35, Folder 345)
  - Chen, Pi-chao - "Population and Health Policy in the People's Republic of China", May 4, 1980-May 24, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 346)
  - Chester, Edward M. - "The Ocular Funds in Systemic Disease-A Clinical Pathological Correlation", April 13, 1972-June 15, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 347)
  - Cohen, Morris L. - "Bibliography of Early American Law", November 2, 1979-October 23, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 348)
  - Colonial Society of Massachusetts - "Medicine in Colonial Massachusetts", November 25, 1980-November 6, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 349)
  - Comroe, Julius H., Jr. - "Top Ten Clinical Advances", August 26, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 350)
  - Cooney, David O., June 24, 1970-July 21, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 351)
  - Council for International Organizations of Medical Sciences (Alfred Gellhorn), February 16, 1978-February 4, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 352)
  - Cournand, Andre, November 9, 1954-March 11, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 353)
  - Crandall, Paul W. - "Epilepsy Originating in the Limbic System", July 13, 1967-April 1, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 354)
  - Dana, Bess - "Education for Community Medicine in Post-Activists Years, 1968-1978", May 4, 1978-December 10, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 355)
  - Denker, David D. - "History of Rutgers Medical School", September 2, 1975-January 20, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 356)
  - Deuschule, Kurt W. - East Harlem Health Resources Handbook Project, April 27, 1972-November 17, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 357)
  - Deuschule, Kurt W. - "International Textbook on Community Medicine", June 5, 1969-May 24, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 358)
  - Diamond, Louis K. - "Diseases of Blood in Children", May 13, 1971-March 3, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 359)
  - Dorwart, Robert A., B. R. Hutcheson and William Meyers, February 8-16, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 360)
  - Epstein, Charles J., March 7, 1972-April 28, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 361)
  - Epstein, Samuel and Howard Hubbard - "Impact of the Automobile on American Life", January 28, 1971-February 25, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 362)
  - Fein, Rashi - "American Health Care System and Health Care Politics", March 14, 1979-November 4, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 363)
  - Flexner, James - "The World of Simon Flexner", May 2, 1980-January 23, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 364)
  - Fox, Daniel M. - "Intellectual History of Contemporary Public Policy for Medical Care", March 24, 1980-August 20, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 365)
  - Fraser, Alan W., September 26, 1968-November 12, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 366)
  - Freiman, David G. - "Study of Teaching Methods in Medical Education", March 8, 1971-May 13, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 367)
  - Fry, Hillary G. - "Oral History of Mental Health", May 13, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 368)
  - Fuchs, Victor R., February 9, 1971-November 11, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 369)
  - Galdston, Iago - "The Social and Historical Foundations of Modern Medicine", June 20, 1976-September 11, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 370)
  - Galdston, Richard - Parent's Center Project for Study and Prevention of Child Abuse, March 31, 1971-April 6, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 371)
  - Gantt, W. Horsley, February 11, 1970-September 18, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 372)
  - Gantt, W. Horsley, February 11, 1970-September 18, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 373)
  - Gantt, W. Horsley, February 11, 1970-September 18, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 374)
  - Gantt, W. Horsley, February 11, 1970-September 18, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 375)
  - Geertsma, Robert H. - "Health Sciences Education and Communication", May 31, 1968-July 30, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 376)
  - Gersh, Isidore (Illustrations), January 4, 1956-April 26, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 377)
  - Glaser, Edmund, December 30, 1969-February 3, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 378)
  - Glueck, Sheldon - "Three Problem Children", November 18, 1970-December 1, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 379)
  - Greenfield, Harry I. - "Hospital Efficiency and Public Policy", November 4, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 380)
  - Grillo, T. Adesanya Ige, April 26, 1967-February 7, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 381)
  - Grinspoon, Lester - "Marihuana Reconsidered", February 18, 1970-April 15, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 382)
  - Goodfield, June (International Health and Biomedicine, Ltd.), October 3, 1977-November 30, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 383)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale, June 9, 1960-September 18, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 384)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale, June 9, 1960-September 18, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 385)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale, June 9, 1960-September 18, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 386)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale (Auxiliary Report), 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 387)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale (Auxiliary Report), December 19, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 388)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale (Auxiliary Report), December 19, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 389)
  - Ham, Thomas Hale (Auxiliary Report), December 19, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 390)
  - Haman, Conrac C. - "Harkness House", September 6, 1978-November 11, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 391)
  - Haman, Conrac C. - "Harkness House", September 6, 1978-November 11, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 392)
  - Hamilton, Leonard D. - "Man in Radiation", February 18, 1972-September 18, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 393)
  - Hamilton, Leonard D. - "Man in Radiation", February 18, 1972-September 18, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 394)
  - Hamilton, Leonard D. - "Man in Radiation", February 18, 1972-September 18, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 395)
  - Hamilton, Leonard D. - "Man in Radiation", February 18, 1972-September 18, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 396)
  - Hardy, Harriet L. - "Occupational Disease", March 11, 1970-May 11, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 397)
  - Harrell, George T., August 4, 1972-April 25, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 398)
  - Harrell, George T., August 4, 1972-April 25, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 399)
  - Harrell, George T., August 4, 1972-April 25, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 400)
  - Hays, Daniel M. - "Biliary Atresia: The Japanese Experience", April 10, 1978-July 5, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 401)
  - Hays, Daniel M. - "Biliary Atresia: The Japanese Experience", April 10, 1978-July 5, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 402)
  - Health, Robert G. - "Studies in Schiziophrenia", September 19, 1972-October 2, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 403)
  - Hechter, Oscar - "Permeability of the Cell Membrane", September 25, 1959-January 31, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 404)
  - Hillman, Robert S. - "Hematology Laboratory Manual", September 16, 1968-February 19, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 405)
  - Hobson, J. Allan - "The Neurobiology of Dreaming", April 26, 1976-May 27, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 406)
  - Hobson, J. Allan - "The Neurobiology of Dreaming", June 8, 1976-August 5, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 407)
  - Hobson, J. Allan - "The Neurobiology of Dreaming", June 8, 1976-August 5, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 408)
  - Hobson, J. Allan - "The Neurobiology of Dreaming", June 8, 1976-August 5, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 409)
  - Hoff, Hebbel E. - "Life of Ramon y Cajal", April 5, 1976-October 5, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 410)
  - Hoff, Hebbel E. - "Life of Ramon y Cajal", April 5, 1976-October 5, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 411)
  - Hoff, Hebbel E. - "Life of Ramon y Cajal", April 5, 1976-October 5, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 412)
  - Hollingsworth, J. Rogers - "A Longitudinal Study of Inequality in Health and Education in Three Western Countries: The United States, the United Kingdom and Sweden", March 30, 1976-January 12, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 413)
  - Holmes, Lewis B. - "Common Birth Defects", June 5, 1979-October 17, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 414)
  - Houston, Charles S. - "Going High", May 2, 1974-February 6, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 415)
  - Horrigan, Daniel and Charles P. Emerson - "Case Development Problems in Hematology" (Revised Edition), February 18, 1970-June 30, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 416)
  - Hume, David - "Hypothalamic Control of Anterior Pituitary Secretion", January 5, 1953-January 25, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 417)
  - Johnson, Davis G. - "U.S. Medical Students, 1950-2000", December 5, 1979-February 9, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 418)
  - Johnson, Davis G. - "U.S. Medical Students, 1950-2000", December 5, 1979-February 9, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 419)
  - Kao, John J. - "Walking on Two Legs: Psychiatry in the People's Republic of China", April 26, 1979-September 11, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 420)
  - Kaplan, Nathan O. - "Biochemical Anthropology", November 12, 1971-April 20, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 421)
  - Karl, Barry D. and Stanley N. Katz - "Private Philanthropy and Public Policy", June 29, 1977-September 10, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 422)
  - Katsh, Seymour, November 17, 1970-December 1, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 423)
  - Kendrick, Mildred - "Quaraticinics: A Definition, Evolution, and Evaluation", March 5-12, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 424)
  - Klein, Hillel - "Survival and Revival: Psychodynamic Studies of Holocaust Survivors and Their Families", August 7, 1974-January 15, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 425)
  - Last, John M. - "Preventive Medicine and Public Health", May 16, 1978-September 12, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 426)
  - Lee, Philip R. and Milton Silverman (Health Policy Program), February 8, 1977-August 15, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 427)
  - Lennard, Henry L. - "Clinical Sociology of Medicine", October 31, 1974-September 11, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 428)
  - Lennard, Henry L. - "Clinical Sociology of Medicine", October 31, 1974-September 11, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 429)
  - Lewis, Walter H. - "Atlas of Plant Aeroallergens in North America", May 19, 1977-January 7, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 430)
  - Lief, Harold I. - "On Becoming a Physician", April 14, 1964-February 12, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 431)
  - Lief, Harold I. - "On Becoming a Physician", April 14, 1964-February 12, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 432)
  - Light, Donald, Jr. - "Impact of Political Idology on Health Care: The German Experience", December 12, 1979-December 12, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 433)
  - Lipowski, Zbigniew J. - "Delirium: Acute Brain Failure in Man", June 11, 1979-September 23, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 434)
  - Lockett, Betty A. - "Politics of Research on Aging", January 5, 1979-July 27, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 435)
  - Luker, Kristin - "Social History of Abortion Activism", January 7, 1980-August 8, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 436)
  - Lyle, Carl B. - "The Crippled Caduceus: A Look at the Practice and Teaching of Internal Medicine at a Community Level", August 12, 1977-February 29, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 437)
  - Lyle, Carl B. - "The Crippled Caduceus: A Look at the Practice and Teaching of Internal Medicine at a Community Level", August 12, 1977-February 29, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 438)
  - Margulies, Harold, April 16-24, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 439)
  - McCauley, E. Hunt - "Economics of Animal Health", March 30, 1973-April 12, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 440)
  - McKenzie-Pollock, James - "Planning a Healthier World", February 15, 1972-July 13, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 441)
  - Miller, Alfred E. - "Sociology and Politics of Health Care", February 2, 1973-July 5, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 442)
  - Miller, George E. - "Teaching and Learning in Medical School", November 26, 1974-September 10, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 443)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction", September 13, 1976-January 14, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 444)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction" (Manuscript), June 1980 (Box 43, Folder 445)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction" (Manuscript), June 1980 (Box 43, Folder 446)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction" (Manuscript), June 1980 (Box 43, Folder 447)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction" (Manuscript), June 1980 (Box 43, Folder 448)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction" (Manuscript), June 1980 (Box 43, Folder 449)
  - Miller, Warren B. - "The Psychology of Reproduction" (Manuscript), June 1980 (Box 43, Folder 450)
  - Morgan, John P. - "The Jake Walk Blues: A Toxicological Tragedy Reflected in American Popular Music", March 26, 1980-July 30, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 451)
  - Musto, David F., June 28, 1971-July 8, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - National Council on Alcoholism - "Advances in Alcoholism" (Mark Galanter), March 3, 1981-October 19, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 453)
  - National Council on Alcoholism - "Currents in Alcoholism" (Proceedings), July 19, 1979-October 16, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 454)
  - Nelson, Russell A., December 11, 1972-January 15, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 455)
  - Olendzki, Margaret - "Health Care Plan for East Harlem-Now", October 8-15, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 456)
  - Olendzki, Margaret - "Health Care Plan for East Harlem-Now", October 8-15, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 457)
  - Olendzki, Margaret - "Health Care Plan for East Harlem-Now", October 8-15, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 458)
  - Page, Ben B. - "The Patient-Physician Relationship", October 9, 1979-July 16, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 459)
  - Pellegrino, Edmund D. - "Albert Flexner Report", September 13, 1971-June 7, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 460)
  - Pribram, Karl H., August 4-10, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 461)
  - Proper, Robert, May 14, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 462)
  - Puck, Theodore T., January 22, 1962-October 8, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 463)
  - Rexford, Eveoleen Naomi - "Public Policy in Child Care", April 21, 1971-September 10, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 464)
  - Rippley, Robert M. - "The Evaluation of Teaching in Medical Schools", March 2, 1978-August 5, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 465)
  - Rosen, George, January 9, 1973-May 2, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 466)
  - Rosenkrantz, Barbara C. - "Recovery and Recidivism in 19th Century American Asylums", October 15, 1979-December 8, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 467)
  - Ross, John - "Learning Disabilities", April 9, 1969-June 5, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 468)
  - Rothstein, William G., August 8-24, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 469)
  - Saunders, Leon Z. - "Evaluation of Veterinary Pathology in Russia", March 10-16, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 470)
  - Scheinberg, Herbert and Irmin Sternlieb - "Copper Metobolism and Wilson's Disease", April 7, 1972-November 18, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 471)
  - Schmitt, Charles, February 4, 1980-September 28, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 472)
  - Scott, Roland B. - "Management of the Child with Sickle Cell Anemia", March 4, 1968-January 16, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 473)
  - Scull, Andrew T. - "The History of Concepts of Insanity in England", February 7, 1980-October 30, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 474)
  - Scull, Andrew T. - "The History of Concepts of Insanity in England", February 7, 1980-October 30, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 475)
  - Scull, Andrew T. - "The History of Concepts of Insanity in England", February 7, 1980-October 30, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 476)
  - Sicherman, Barbara - "Selected Papers of Alice Hamilton", November 7, 1974-July 1, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 477)
  - Sicherman, Barbara - "Selected Papers of Alice Hamilton", November 7, 1974-July 1, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 478)
  - Sicherman, Barbara - "The Paradox of Prudence: Mental Health in the Gilded Age", No Date (Box 45, Folder 479)
  - Sicherman, Barbara - "Wear and Tear: Doctors, Patients and the Rise of Neurasthenia", No Date (Box 45, Folder 480)
  - Sidel, Victor - "The Barefoot Doctors of the People's Republic of China", September 15, 1971-December 7, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 481)
  - Solnit, Albert J. and Sally Provence - Yale Longitudinal Study of Personality Development, November 22, 1978-December 12, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 482)
  - Starr, Arnold - "Neurophysiological Mechanisms of the Auditory System", May 19, 1971-July 9, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 483)
  - Stewart, Peter A. - "Acid-base Physiology and Medicine", January 17, 1973-May 25, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 484)
  - Stone, Alan A. - "Law and Morality: Essays and Analysis", March 4, 1980-August 18, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 485)
  - Stone, Alan A. - "Law and Morality: Essays and Analysis", March 4, 1980-August 18, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 486)
  - Stone, Alan A. - "Law and Morality: Essays and Analysis", March 4, 1980-August 18, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 487)
  - Stratmann, William C. - "Genesee Experiment: Study of Change at a Community Hospital", October 11, 1974-January 6, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 488)
  - Stratmann, William C. - "Genesee Experiment: Study of Change at a Community Hospital", October 11, 1974-January 6, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 489)
  - Strickland, Stephen and Douglass Cater - "TV and Social Behavior of Your Child", February 4, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 490)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Galleys I), [1950] (Box 47, Folder 491)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Galleys I), [1950] (Box 47, Folder 492)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Galleys II), [1951] (Box 47, Folder 493)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Illustrations), May 3, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 494)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted - Confidential material. Requires prior archival review.
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Illustrations), May 3, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 495)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Illustrations), May 3, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 496)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Index), [1951] (Box 47, Folder 497)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Manuscript), [1951] (Box 47, Folder 498)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Notes on Illustrations), March 10, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 499)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Metabolic Hemeostasis", January 14, 1971-February 2, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 500)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Syllabus on Pediatric Endocrinology", April 1, 1960-February 3, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 501)
  - Thompson, E. Brad - "Molecular Mechanisms of Glucocorticoid Action", April 10, 1974-September 11, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 502)
  - Thorne, Samuel E. - "Year Book of Richard II, Years 8-10", April 7, 1976-September 10, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 503)
  - Troupin, James L. - "Public Health Physicians 1911-1970", February 23, 1972-March 17, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 504)
  - Tulane University, June 20, 1961-June 27, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 505)
  - Valadian, Isabelle and Robert B. Reed - "Adult Health Related to Child Health and Development", April 7, 1970-November 5, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 506)
  - Valadian, Isabelle and Robert B. Reed - "Adult Health Related to Child Health and Development", April 7, 1970-November 5, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 507)
  - Van Itallie, Theodore B. - "Clinical Nutrition and Metabolism", December 20, 1967-April 23, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 508)
  - Van Itallie, Theodore B. - "Clinical Nutrition and Metabolism", December 20, 1967-April 23, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 509)
  - Van Itallie, Theodore B. - "Clinical Nutrition and Metabolism", December 20, 1967-April 23, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 510)
  - Valasques, M. Tulio - "High Altitude Nature Living in the Andes", May 24, 1974-July 6, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 511)
  - Wacher, Warren E. C. - "Magnexium Metabolism in Human Disease States", July 12, 1976-October 14, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 512)
  - Wald, Florence - "Study of Care for the Terminally Ill in Existing Health Care System", July 14, 1978-July 30, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 513)
  - Wang, Shih-Chun - "Physiology of the Brain Stem", June 17, 1976-June 23, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 514)
  - Waring, George O., Peter Laibson and Merlyn Rodriques - "Clinicopathologic correlations in Corneal Disease", August 19, 1976-July 23, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 515)
  - Warren, James V. - "The Clinical Training of the Medical Student", February 8, 1979-September 11, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 516)
  - Warren, Kenneth - "Medical Libraries: Their Structure and Dynamics", December 10, 1969-March 3, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 517)
  - Webster, Thomas G., Irving N. Berlin and Joseph D. Noshpitz - "Basic Handbook of Child Psychiatry", May 9, 1975-March 1, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 518)
  - Wedgwood, Ralph J. - "Child Health and Public Policy", January 16, 1969-July 9, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 519)
  - Weitzman, Elliot D. - "Biological Rhythms in Man", November 12, 1973-July 9, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 520)
  - Wennberg, John E. and Alan M. Gittelsohn - "Studies of Health Care in Vermont", December 16, 1974-February 27, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 521)
  - Wennberg, John E. and Alan M. Gittelsohn - "Studies of Health Care in Vermont", December 16, 1974-February 27, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 522)
  - White, Kerr - "Clinical Preventive Medicine", November 9, 1959-September 23, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 523)
  - White, Kerr and Franklin Williams - "Patient Referrals and the University Clinic", September 10, 1958-March 18, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 524)
  - White, Kerr and Franklin Williams - "Patient Referrals and the University Clinic", September 10, 1958-March 18, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 525)
  - White, Kerr and Franklin Williams - "Patient Referrals and the University Clinic", September 10, 1958-March 18, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 526)
  - Wilens, Sigmund L. - "Morphology of Cardiovascular Disease", October 31, 1972-November 16, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 527)
  - Willard, Harold N. - "The Teaching of General Internal Medicine", July 12, 1978-April 27, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 528)
  - Williams, Greer - "Western Reserve's Experiment in Medical Education and Its Outcome", August 8, 1978-August 23, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 529)
  - Williams, Ralph C. - "Immune Complexes in Clinical and Experimental Medicine", January 28, 1978-October 16, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 530)
  - Williams, Richard A. - "Black Related Diseases", September 16, 1971-November 9, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 531)
  - Wilson, Marjorie P. - "Evolution of Medical School", May 6, 1976-July 29, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 532)
  - Wilson, Marjorie P. - "Evolution of Medical School", May 6, 1976-July 29, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 533)